fashionfabricsclub.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy | Discount By The Yard | Fashion Fabrics

The privacy of our visitors to fashionfabricsclub.com is important to us. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product, or service information, etc.
  * Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, contact customerservice@fashionfabricsclub.com.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature.

We may share your personally-identifiable information, including your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partner will make the data we provide anonymous. To choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner, please send notification to customerservice@fashionfabricsclub.com

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. These security measures include password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. We have the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and can only be accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We utilize cookie technology to serve ads on behalf of fashionfabricsclub.com. You have the option to refuse cookies altogether by turning them off in your browser

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

fashionfabricsclub.com  
10490 Baur Blvd.  
St. Louis, MO 63132  
USA

## Email Us
